

Massimiliano Bruni

Email: massimiliano.bruni@icloud.com | Mobile: +39 334 924 0665

PROFILE

I am a Software Engineer specialized in Ma- OUTFITTERY chine Learning. During my career I have real- SOFTWARE ENGINEER - MACHINE LEARNING ized and put into production various projects, Dec 2022 - present | Berlin (Full Remote) technology and I like working on innovative projects. I work methodically, precisely and hard-working and pragmatic.

LINKS

Github://Maxinho96

LinkedIn://Massimiliano Bruni Medium://Massimiliano Bruni YouTube://Massimiliano Bruni

LANGUAGES

Italian: Native

English: Fluent (B2/C1 level)

SKILLS

HARD SKILLS

Advanced: Python • Machine Learning FastAPI • Flask • AWS • Docker • Kubernetes Airflow • Elasticsearch • Opensearch Kibana • PostgreSQL • Linux • Bash • Git Intermediate: Pandas • Polars • RabbitMQ Huggingface Transformers • Rasa Chatbot Basic: Golang • Java • Keras • TensorFlow Terraform • Cloudformation • Logstash

SOFT SKILLS

Problem solving, for the Engineering studies. **Team working**, for the projects I worked on. Communication, for the experiences as private tutor and library assistant.

Learning, for my passion to discover the world.

CERTIFICATIONS

Year	Released by	Certificate
2022	Rasa chatbot	Rasa Developer
		Certification
2021	Coursera	Deep Learning
		Specialization
2020	Italian State	Software
		Engineering License
2015	Cambridge	B2 First
2015	Cisco	CCNA Discovery

HOBBIES

Sports • Technology news • Videogames Board games • Mangas • Hangout

EXPERIENCE

both proprietaries and Open Source. I love I am responsible of developing and maintaining Machine Learning microservices and pipelines in the Data Science team. I also take architectural decisions and I take care of the cloud infrastructure.

with attention to details. I am rational, diligent, Technologies: Python • FastAPI • Flask • AWS • Docker • Kubernetes • Airflow • Opensearch • Kibana • PostgreSQL • Pandas • Polars • RabbitMQ • Terraform • Cloudformation

HCL SOFTWARE

SOFTWARE ENGINEER - MACHINE LEARNING

May 2021 - Nov 2022 | Rome (Hybrid)

I was responsible of developing the Python backend and the training process of new projects that require Machine Learning. I was also involved in the product delivery process in both cloud and on-premise environments.

Technologies: Python • Pandas • Huggingface Transformers • Rasa • FastAPI • Bash • Docker • Kubernetes • Elasticsearch • Kibana • Logstash

ASKDATA

MACHINE LEARNING ENGINEER

September 2020 - April 2021 | Rome (Full Remote)

I was responsible of R&D and releasing in production Deep Learning models in the NLP field involving Text Summarization, Machine Translation, Named Entity Recognition and Semantic

Technologies: Python • Pandas • Huggingface Transformers • Flask • FastAPI

EDUCATION

ITALIAN RESEARCH CENTER (CNR)

ADVANCED SCHOOL IN ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE

Practical school with focus on Machine Learning Applications. October 2019 - April 2020 | Rome

UNIVERSITÀ DEGLI STUDI ROMA TRE

BACHELOR'S AND MASTER'S DEGREE IN COMPUTER SCIENCE ENGINEERING

September 2015 - July 2020 | Rome

Grade: 110/110 cum laude

PROJECTS

CLARA (LINK)

A chatbot virtual assistant for Workload Automation.

Al Data Advisor (Link)

An Anomaly Detection System for Workload Automation.

HUMAN2SQL (LINK)

Translation from spoken language to SQL language.

VIDEO SURVEILLANCE SYSTEM (LINK) OBJECT DETECTION WITH DRONE (LINK) TELEGRAM BOT: IMAGE CLASSIFIER (LINK)

OPEN SOURCE CONTRIBUTIONS

TRAINING GROUNDS (LINK)

Outfittery's Data Science Framework.

RASA CHATBOT FRAMEWORK (LINK)

HUGGINGFACE TRANSFORMERS (LINK)

YOLOV3 TENSORFLOW IMPLEMENTATION (LINK)

I authorize to use and process my personal details contained in this document.